// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "How do you insert COMMENTS in Java code?",
    answer: "// This is a comment",
    options: [
      "# This is a comment",
      "// This is a comment",
      "** This is a comment",
      "/$ This is a comment"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "How do you create a variable with the floating number 2.8?",
    answer: "float x = 2.8f;",
    options: [
      "x = 2.8f;",
      "float x = 2.8f;",
      "byte x = 2.8f",
      "int x = 2.8f;"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which method can be used to return a string in upper case letters?",
    answer: "toUpperCase()",
    options: [
      "upperCase()",
      "tuc()",
      "touppercase()",
      "toUpperCase()"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "To declare an array in Java, define the variable type with:",
    answer: "[]",
    options: [
      "{}",
      "()",
      "[]",
      "<>"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "How do you create a method in Java?",
    answer: "methodName()",
    options: [
      "methodName.",
      "methodName()",
      "(methodName)",
      "methodName[]"
    ]
  },
  
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which keyword is used to create a class in Java?",
    answer: "class",
    options: [
      "MyClass",
      "className",
      "class()",
      "class"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which method can be used to find the highest value of x and y?",
    answer: "Math.max(x,y)",
    options: [
      "Math.maximum(x,y)",
      "Math.max(x,y)",
      "Math.largest(x,y)",
      "Math.maxNum(x,y)"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which keyword is used to import a package from the Java API library?",
    answer: "import",
    options: [
      "getlib",
      "package",
      "import",
      "lib"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which statement is used to stop a loop?",
    answer: "break",
    options: [
      "stop",
      "break",
      "return",
      "exit"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "How do you start writing a while loop in Java?",
    answer: "while (x > y)",
    options: [
      "while x > y {",
      "x > y while {",
      "while (x > y)",
      "while x > y:"
    ]
  },
];